[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Its normal for blood pressure to be quite elevated during strenuous activity.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The mathematical constant Pi has an important role in calculating the period of a pendulum.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What profession does the movie Black Dog and its soundtrack pertain to?", "correct_answer": "Truck Driving", "incorrect_answers": ["Musician", "Navy Seal", "Police Officer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following was NOT used to kill the snakes in the movie Snakes on a Plane?", "correct_answer": "Gun", "incorrect_answers": ["Axe", "Microwave", "Spear Gun"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "John Steinbeck wrote the highly acclaimed novel The Grapes of Wrath. Where does the title come from?", "correct_answer": "The Battle Hymn of the Republic", "incorrect_answers": ["A poem by Shakespeare", "A famous sermon by Cotton Mather", "The Bible"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When did a war start over a postage stamp?", "correct_answer": "1932", "incorrect_answers": ["1833", "1896", "1847"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Harry Caul, the protagonist of the film The Conversation?", "correct_answer": "Gene Hackman", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Duvall", "John  Garfield", "Jon Voight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which show was the first to have an episode which dealt with abortion?", "correct_answer": "Maude", "incorrect_answers": ["Room 222", "All in the Family", "Good Times"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why did Kate Winslet decide she would never work with director James Cameron again during the filming of the 1997 movie Titanic?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["She got sick from flu.", "She chipped her elbow bone.", "She almost drowned."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is trying to take over Costa Luna in the film Princess Protection Program?", "correct_answer": "General Kane", "incorrect_answers": ["General Luis", "General Candy Cane", "General Cane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements if true about a cat?", "correct_answer": "Their urine glows under a black light.", "incorrect_answers": ["Normal body temperature for a a cat is 95 degrees Fahrenheit.", "They take about 50 breaths per minute.", "They walk on the bottoms of their feet."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what sport was Roy Munson crowned the 1979 Iowa State Champion in the movie Kingpin?", "correct_answer": "Bowling", "incorrect_answers": ["Golf", "Tennis", "Wrestling"]}]